<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

<channel>
  <title>Rocco's LinkedIn SSI Micro-tips</title>
  <link>https://www.linkedin.com/in/roccorusso</link>
  <description>Micro-tips to improve your LinkedIn SSI</description>

  <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xdemocle/xdemocle/refs/heads/master/1-20.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 1: Polish Your Profile Picture</title>
    <description>
      You wouldn't show up to an interview in your pajamas (hopefully). Your profile photo is your first impression.
      Make it clear, professional, and smile like you just passed all your unit tests on the first try.
      Follow me or drop a message if you’re unsure about your current photo!
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 2: Write a Killer Headline</title>
    <description>
      "Software Engineer" is fine. "JavaScript Wizard turning coffee into code" is better.
      Make your headline punchy and specific. Show some personality.
      Need a headline refresh? Connect with me or ping me.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 3: Fill Out Your ‘About’ Section</title>
    <description>
      If your “About” says nothing, recruiters will assume you ghost your own career.
      Add 3-5 sentences. Say what you do, how you do it, and what lights your brain on fire.
      Want eyes on your About section? I'm here.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 4: Customize Your Banner</title>
    <description>
      Default banners scream, “I forgot this part.”
      Upload something that reflects you — code snippet, skyline, clean design.
      Need a free tool? Canva’s your friend.
      Ask if you need help choosing the right vibe.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 5: Connect With Purpose</title>
    <description>
      Stop blindly connecting like it’s Pokémon Go.
      Target people in your industry, tech you love, or companies you want.
      Attach a short message. It works wonders.
      Want help crafting it? Message me!
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 6: Engage Weekly</title>
    <description>
      Liking one post per month isn’t engagement. It's lurking.
      Comment on posts, join conversations, and show you're alive.
      Think of LinkedIn like a daily standup — show up.
      Let’s engage! Comment something below.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 7: Share a Tip Once a Week</title>
    <description>
      You’ve learned something cool? Share it.
      Doesn’t need to be earth-shattering. A bug you fixed counts.
      Keep it simple and real.
      Tag me if you post — I’ll cheer you on.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 8: Update Your Skills</title>
    <description>
      Your profile still says “jQuery Master”? Oof.
      Update your tech stack. Add relevant skills. Remove the relics.
      Need help modernizing it? I got you.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 9: Follow Industry Leaders</title>
    <description>
      Follow people who post value. Not just meme lords.
      Your feed will get smarter, and you’ll get ideas for your own posts.
      Who do you follow? Let me know!
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 10: Use the Featured Section Wisely</title>
    <description>
      Pin your best work: blog posts, portfolio, project demos.
      Make it easy for recruiters to see your skills.
      No feature = missed opportunity.
      Want me to review yours? DM me.
    </description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 11: Optimize Your Experience Section</title>
    <description>
      Your experience section should be detailed but concise. Highlight your achievements and the impact you made in each role.
      Use bullet points to make it scannable.
      Need help refining it? Reach out!
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 12: Use Keywords Strategically</title>
    <description>
      Recruiters use keywords to find candidates. Make sure your profile includes relevant keywords for your industry and skills.
      Include them naturally in your headline, about section, and experience.
      Want a keyword review? Drop me a message.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 13: Get Recommendations</title>
    <description>
      Recommendations from colleagues and managers add credibility to your profile.
      Don’t be shy to ask for them. Offer to write one in return.
      Need tips on asking for recommendations? I’m here to help.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 14: Join Relevant Groups</title>
    <description>
      Joining groups related to your industry can help you stay updated and network with professionals.
      Participate in discussions and share your insights.
      Which groups are you part of? Let me know!
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 15: Use LinkedIn Stories</title>
    <description>
      LinkedIn Stories are a great way to share quick updates and behind-the-scenes content.
      Use them to show your personality and engage with your network.
      Need ideas for Stories? Message me!
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 16: Endorse Others</title>
    <description>
      Endorsing others for their skills can encourage them to endorse you back.
      It’s a simple way to build mutual support.
      Want to know who to endorse? Connect with me.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 17: Use LinkedIn Polls</title>
    <description>
      Polls are an engaging way to gather opinions and start conversations.
      Create polls related to your industry or topics you’re passionate about.
      Need help crafting a poll? I’m here.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 18: Keep Your Profile Public</title>
    <description>
      Make sure your profile is visible to everyone. A private profile limits your opportunities.
      Adjust your privacy settings to maximize your visibility.
      Need help with settings? Drop me a message.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 19: Use LinkedIn Articles</title>
    <description>
      Writing articles on LinkedIn can showcase your expertise and thought leadership.
      Share your knowledge, insights, and experiences.
      Want feedback on your article? Ping me!
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Micro-tip 20: Regularly Update Your Profile</title>
    <description>
      Keep your profile up-to-date with your latest achievements, projects, and skills.
      A stale profile can make you look inactive.
      Need a profile review? I got you.
    </description>
  </item>

</channel>
</rss>
